propgo.com 2017-12-02

# PropGO Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  

PropGO.com respects your privacy and recognizes the importance of protecting information collected from you through PropGO.com's Web site, related data, and/or related services (collectively, the "Services"). We have adopted this privacy policy. PropGO.com will comply with this policy, and applicable privacy-related law, when we gather and use information from users of the Services. 

This policy is current as of its last revision date below. However, please note that this policy may be amended from time to time to reflect changes and additions to the privacy policy. You should check back for the most current version before relying on any of the provisions in this privacy policy. 

**Collection of Information**

PropGO.com collects a variety of information relating to usage of the Services.

• **Information you provide.** You may provide information in connection with your use of the Services, such as information about homes. You may also provide us information about yourself, such as providing your e-mail address so we can send you information about the Services, or sending us e-mail. We may combine this information with other information we collect from the Services or from other companies.   
• **Cookies.** Cookies are bits of electronic information that can be transferred to a user's computer to uniquely identify the user's browser. When you visit the Services, we place one or more cookies on your computer. The use of cookies helps us improve the quality of the Services in various ways, such as identifying which Services are most interesting to you, or storing information you may want to retrieve on a regular basis or tracking user trends. You may adjust settings on your browser to refuse cookies. Some Services and features may not function property if you disable cookies.   
• **Usage logs.** When you access the Services, your computer communicates a variety of information to computer servers operating the Services, including the existence of cookies, your Internet Protocol address, and information about your browser program. Your usage also creates a record of what information you are requesting from the Services.   
**Usage and Disclosure**

In general, PropGO.com uses the information collected to provide the Services and to communicate with you. The information that you choose to provide in a public area of the Services will not be protected by this privacy policy.

We will only share personal information that you provide outside the public areas of the Services in the following circumstances:

• **Consent.** When you consent or direct PropGO.com to share the information.   
• **Affiliates and service providers.** When PropGO.com provides personal information to our affiliated companies or service providers to manage and use on our behalf, consistent with the terms of this privacy policy.   
• **Legal Obligation or Protection from Harm.** When PropGO.com has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the personal information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any requirement of law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce or investigate a potential violation of the, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise respond to fraud, security or technical concerns, or (d) protect the rights, property, or safety of PropGO.com, its users, or the public against harm.   
• **Merger or sale.** When and if PropGO.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its business, personal information may be transferred along with the business. 

We may share with third parties aggregate information or information that does not personally identify individuals. 

**Opting Out**

If you want PropGO.com to cease sending you e-mail about the Services, you can discontinue such communication by following the instructions included in our e-mail.

**Collection of Information by Ad Servers**

PropGO.com may use a third party to present or serve advertisements that you may see at PropGO.com Web pages. These third-party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third-party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy policy. 

**Third Party Web Sites**

The Services may include links to the Web sites of other companies and/or individuals. These third party Web sites may collect personal information about users on those Web sites, and PropGO.com's privacy policy does not extend to these external Web sites and third parties. Please refer directly to these third parties and Web sites regarding their privacy policies.

**Storage and Security of Information**

Personal information will be processed and stored by PropGO.com in databases hosted in the United States and other countries where applicable. PropGO is not responsible for any system breach or unauthorized hacking event whether known or unknown that exposes our user’s information. PropGO.com has taken reasonable steps to protect the information users share with us, including, but not limited to, setup of processes, equipment and software to avoid unauthorized access or disclosure of this information.

**Contacting PropGO.com**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or the privacy practices of PropGO.com, please contact us by e-mailing info@PropGO.com .
